I'm on a journey out to see the world.
While I'm on my own, I've
yet to reach the end.
So won't you come along with me right now?
Surely then we can!
Follow me now as we
journey on from sea to sea.
For that treasure known
by everybody as one piece.
Even though they laugh and
say it's just a fantasy.
We are going, there's no doubt we go.
Cause we can feel the
rush of energy overcome.
It will lead the way.
Keep pretending that you know what to do.
Books will only get in the way.
No guides for today.
Do not worry soon.
The rain will be gone with the wind.
Keep your chin up, raise the anchor.
Now that's what you'll do.
Give it time and calm the storm
that you have built within.
Come and have never get number two.
Once tomorrow's wind picks up.
We set stuff cause we can't.
Fresh enough, stand tall and
take a look at one of you.
All the journey makes
me want to see somebody.
There are things out there
you just won't believe.
Beyond your wildest dreams.
Don't think for a second.
It's not the truth.
That's the story.
Most will believe.
Not me.
Come and see.
I am on a journey.
Out to sea.
The world done on.
On my own.
I've got my group of friends.
Together we've got our way.
That's how it's done.
Says your captain.
Who says it can't be done.
We haven't even tried.
Gotta just believe we'll
make it to the end.
I just wanna do it all right now.
Together surely we can.
Yes, we can.
You can.
Just take this moment in.
We can.
I can.
Just take this feeling in.
Right now.
Oh yes, we can.
Yes, we can!
The ancient elephant elephant fruit, huh?
That's a rare power you nabbed there.
Who knew you had so many
warriors at your disposal?
Are you gotta sure you want to do this,
you boys can still cut
your losses, master here.
We got as many warriors as a
major nation, all ready to go.
Beppo, you gotta are
all still under my care.
Stand down—this isn't your fight!
fight Not if I get a say in it, Master!
Sorry!
I might be a pirate, but
this land is still my home!
And as his friends, we'll fight too!
Heh!
That don't impress me.
It will destroy everything.
Try it and see what happens.
It's morning already?
Haven't you, Karoo, had enough yet?
We continued our tactic of
rotating our forces in shifts.
Duke Dogstorm valiantly
fought through the day,
while Master Cat Viper
zealously defended the night.
Unfortunately,
it was difficult to keep up with Jack's
reinforcements arriving
in droves by the sea.
It felt as if we were fighting
an unstoppable army of zombies.
However, with perseverance, we
steadily overcame the enemy.
Yet despite our efforts, there was one
thing that we simply could not overcome.
Jack himself!
That man truly is a monster.
So even this big dog duke couldn't
take down that guy from Kaido's crew?
That's crazy!
But the same applied to Jack as well.
He started to struggle, and
he wasn't able to keep up.
Juggling both of our rulers wore him down.
But on the fifth day, he
unleashed a weapon in desperation.
It was...
A poison gas.
We stood no chance.
Instantaneously, the deadly
gas spread through the land.
How could we ever escape such a thing?
It was bad. We were powerless.
it swallowed up the entire
city we were all completely
paralyzed only those who evacuated
to the fortress were able to
survive the assaults as for
what happened next I don't even
want to say it answer the
question where do mongrels hide the
They kept on insisting that we
were hiding the truth from them.
They brought our land to
ruin one Mink at a time.
Sadly, when they found Master
Cat Viper and all of his men,
they were still paralyzed by the gas.
They tried interrogating them,
but when that got them nowhere...
The mighty were brutally crucified
and subjected to torture.
Where is the Wano warrior?
I don't know.
We would never hide a samurai!
Please stop this madness.
My poor people know nothing.
Don't hurt them.
This massacre is pointless.
It's its cruelty.
I'll remember you, Karoo, Jack.
After I'm gone, I'll haunt you to
the day you die with my cat's curse!
The slaughter continued for an entire day.
And on the sixth day.
I guess he must have had
his fill of destruction.
Or grown tired of the same answer.
He left behind a few dozen men.
And suddenly departed from the island.
I'm so sorry.
It sounds like you're
all lucky to be alive.
And yet, in the end,
we were spared by fate.
How long have you been awake?
The truth became apparent after reading
Jack's obituary in the newspaper.
Oh, so that was the jerk.
The day that Jack
finally departed from our
beloved land was the day
Yugarra drowned Doflamingo.
I realized he left this land in order
to liberate Doflamingo from captivity.
They must have been bound
by some deep connection.
In other words,
the ones who truly drove that rootless
creature from our home was you, Karoo.
He fell asleep!
I see.
Knowing that, I now feel even more
gratitude towards all of you, Tia.
The day after Doflamingo was
defeated was the same day we arrived!
Is that...Zoom?!
I'll warn you!
Landing here is a big mistake!
Curse you all!
Shut up and carry us!
Mark my words!
You will rule this day!
This is weird.
Sanji, wait up.
The gates broke?
Something nasty forced this
thing open, or so it appears.
This place must have been invaded.
An invasion?
Are we in danger? Hey, Brooke.
Stay here and protect Nami.
I'll check out the scene
no problemo my man,
but perhaps I should look
after old Nami as well
Chopper Caesar. Let's go.
Why me too?
Have a good time.
This place looks abandoned.
There's no guard in sight.
What could have happened?
Did that voice come from her?
Okay, think.
Oh, he definitely looks like a bad guy.
Then she needs my help.
This way!
Where do you think
you're going, Squirrely?
We just want to crucify you
and ask you a few questions.
Huh? Who are they?
Hey, Brooke, can you
take them out? Indeed.
Huh?
Welcome to the Soul Parade.
Now, Iceburn.
All right!
Bokichi splinted!
Thank you, Brooke. Good job.
A talking skeleton and a floating eel?
Scary!
Hey, wait!
What's going on around here?
Is this normal?
What's going on with this place?
There's gas everywhere.
Are all these fallen people animals?
They're the mink tribe, you idiot!
Don't you know anything?
We should head back to the forest
before we succumb to the gas ourselves.
Hey, Yugara!
Seems like this batch didn't
completely finish the job.
Please tell me you're not their allies.
My name's Pedro.
We need your help.
Please, I beg of Yugara.
Duke Dogstorm and Master Cat Viper are
in need of urgent medical assistance.
Their lives are at stake.
The world still needs them.
You must help.
Above all else, those two must live.
Please, don't let them die!
What a disaster.
The whole country's been
devastated by this gas.
I'm getting goosebumps seeing its power.
What's so funny, you creep?
That gas is named Karoo.
It's a concoction of my own making.
What the hell'd you just say?
What I said is that I made that gas.
Ah?
Why does that make me the bad guy here?
I wasn't the one who used it, you know?
I can't wait till this guy's gone.
If you never made the junk in
the first place, they'd be fine.
Now you better neutralize
it with your power.
Do it!
and then you're gonna make them an
antidote and you're not gonna complain.
considering how much gas
has already cleared away,
I'd estimate they have about a day
left again, ah, hey, stop that!
Don't just assume the
underdogs were the good
guys just so you know the
Ming tribe is well known
for their hatred of
humans and their fighting
ability—maybe it's better
if they die the moment we.
we If we revive them,
they'll rip us to shreds!
Rip us to shreds? Really?
Oh, no!
I can't move!
Chopper!
Oh, come on.
Couldn't you have been a
little bit gentler with me?
Stop complaining.
I saved you, didn't I?
That was Nami's voice.
Now you listen.
Before I get back here,
you better have this poison gas
crab cleaned up, you hear me?
And why should I? Hey, look.
Want to play games with me?
How about I hunt this?
All right, cheetah.
Sanji, just go, I'll look after him.
Cool, thanks.
That's her!
Brooke, keep him occupied!
Huh, huh?
Yuba!
Luton!
Mowat!
Master Sheepshead, no!
All of you, retreat now!
Master Sheepshead has been defeated!
But we haven't found the samurai yet!
He's not come out, even
after we pushed him this far.
Go report that there's
no samurai here! Right!
Neutralize the gas already!
You're no fun, but fine!
Fine, I'll do it!
You happy now?
Karoo, neutralizing gas!
Curse you! No!
No!
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH Cough.
Cough.
Cough. Cough.
Cough. Good.
Hey, everybody!
Get over here!
Cough.
It's Chopper Emon!
Let us make haste! You're right!
We've got no time to lose!
Cough.
Th-this is dreadful.
How sad.
Caesar's weapon killed them all?
Yeah. Damn shame.
Those scumbags pretty much
wiped out this whole country.
The people who attacked us? How awful!
At least Caesar was able to
clear the poison from this area.
Since they did something this drastic,
there's a good chance there's
still some enemies hiding.
So be on your guard.
According to Gas Hole over here, the
Mink tribe isn't too fond of humans.
I hate to say it, but we might end
up regretting saving them if we do.
Don't move!
Are you two with Jack?
Nami!
Wait, please! Let's talk!
She's weak from the gas!
Nami!
She has an explosive!
Get away!
No, die!
I'll never forgive you, Tia!
My people didn't deserve any of this!
There's nothing to gain from slaying us!
The person you're seeking isn't here!
How much of a thousand-year
history must you
do to destroy before your
bloodlust is satisfied?
Wanda, stop!
Don't hurt them!
They saved me!
Huh? Tristan?
Jack's men left already! Please!
They aren't with them!
They left?
You're sure?
pedro wanda they didn't come
here to fight their allies
using strange magic they
cleared out the poison
we are indebted to them
i didn't notice but
the smog is gone what
are your names tell me
what are you doing let's
go chopper I'm serious.
Look, it's been at least
a day since the attack.
To counteract the poison, they need
to have the antidote by 48 hours!
Or else they'll all die! What's that?
If we're gonna save everyone in the
country, we don't have a second to spare!
Where's the hospital?
I need more supplies right now!
Gather anyone who's well enough to assist!
Sure. I'm a nurse.
I can help too.
If...
you do...
want the help?
Yes.
I was afraid that everybody would die.
I promise, they won't.
We'll need your help, though.
There, you'll feel better shortly.
Try those eyes!
Let's get you workin'!
U .T.
saved our civilization.
Even though we were strangers.
We will never forget the
compassion you've shown.
We will repay U .T. someday! Please!
No need I can't believe
things are that tire that's
why you were welcoming
toward us it makes sense now
Damn it that Jack jerk makes
me so mad someday I'm gonna
whoop him and Kaido too They
mentioned that he's dead already.
I'm not sure.
It's hard to believe that's true.
Especially if Yutia had seen his strength.
Keep talking, but I gotta go.
Have something to do? What's up?
Now that the sun's down,
time for the night shift.
I need to examine Cat
Viper and the Guardians.
Right.
Let's go by Warnie.
By the way, Wanda, it's late.
Aren't you tired yet?
I'm fine.
After all, I am a king's bird.
A king's bird?
Yes,
I have a special position
in which I act as
a go-between for the
kings of day and night.
I'm allowed to be active
no matter the time.
Wow, you're pretty important, huh?
I must report to him that Duke
Dogstorm is alive and well,
although he'll claim he doesn't care.
I'm coming!
Let's go meet him!
It sounds cool!
Ah, yes, I shall go, too.
I am quite fond of the
fellow to Master Cat Viper.
I see it's a full moon tonight, but
fortunately for us, the clouds are thick.
Have a safe trip. Later.
Thanks for making time to
give us a ride, Carrot.
No biggie.
Besides, I'm a king bird, too.
Anyway, Wanda, you weren't done
telling us the whole story.
Oh, yeah.
We never found out where that dumbass
cook and gas he scurried off to.
Perhaps I am better suited to finish this.
To put it frankly,
the majority of the Minx are unaware of
what exactly transpired after that point.
Their land had already been ravaged,
and we didn't want to cause
them any more distress.
The event that happened
two days ago was so
utterly terrible that
we've kept it a secret.
Please brace yourselves; I
say this with a heavy heart,
though my ribcage is most assuredly empty.
But I fear our dear friend Sanji
may never return to our side, huh?
You're kidding me, right?
Why Brook?
What kind of crap is that?
He said in his letter that he would
come back; we warned you this.
The situation's pretty complicated.
He wouldn't lie to us!
I believe Sanji, end of story!
All right, all right.
Now take it easy, Luffy.
Allow me to catch you up to the present.
As you know, Zo is known
as a Phantom Island.
It's a living creature,
always on the move,
so you can't exactly
find it with a Log Pose,
much less locate it on a map.
However,
we made a mistake and failed
to take one thing into account
as we were dodging the enemy
ship we gave
them vital info
how could we escape when they
knew where we were going next
and unluckily someone from this
phantom island was aboard the
enemy ship.
Long story short,
the people who followed us
here two days ago were the big
mom pirates.
We're here.
You got it.
You can count on us, mama.
Us two should be more than
enough.
So is my homeland after all. Get out!